{
    "title": "Baseball",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "This pitcher threw three no-hitters in his career, and set a record for throwing 12 one-hitters. Who is this Hall of Fame great?",
            "choices": [
                "Sandy Koufax",
                "Bob Feller",
                "Nolan Ryan",
                "Cy Young"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Tim Wakefield of the Boston Red Sox tied a Major League record in 2004. What did Tim accomplish?",
            "choices": [
                "Hit four consecutive batters",
                "Starting pitcher for both games of a doubleheader, and won them both",
                "Pitched a game that he hit three home runs in",
                "Gave up six home runs in a game"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Which player in 1992 tied a record for being walked in seven consecutive at-bats?",
            "choices": [
                "Jose Canseco",
                "Albert Belle",
                "Barry Bonds",
                "Mark McGwire"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "J.R. Richard of the Houston Astros set a modern-day record for throwing six wild pitches in a game in 1979. Which pitcher tied that record less than four months later?",
            "choices": [
                "Phil Niekro",
                "Mike Morgan",
                "Nolan Ryan",
                "Greg Pinchbeck"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Larry Walker of the Colorado Rockies tied a record in April 1998 for doing what?",
            "choices": [
                "Played all the fielding positions in one game",
                "Was thrown out twice caught stealing in the same inning",
                "Hit nine home runs in nine consecutive at-bats",
                "Hit for the cyle in one game, and it included a grand slam"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Which modern-day Major League pitcher set a record for losing 18 consecutive games?",
            "choices": [
                "Roger Craig",
                "Randy Jones",
                "Mike Maroth",
                "Pat Caraway"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Which player set a record for playing on the same team for 23 seasons?",
            "choices": [
                "Cal Ripken Jr.",
                "Brooks Robinson",
                "Mel Ott",
                "Eddie Collins"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Which player in the 1950s set a record for getting 12 hits in 12 consecutive at-bats?",
            "choices": [
                "Ted Williams",
                "Walt Dropo",
                "Gil McDougald",
                "Hank Bauer"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This pitcher must have had a lot of nervous ticks in the season because he set a Major League record for committing 16 balks. Who was this multiple 20-game winner?",
            "choices": [
                "Juan Marichal",
                "Warren Spahn",
                "Dave Stewart",
                "Mickey Lolich"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the first batter in Major League history to strike out 200 times in a season?",
            "choices": [
                "Bobby Bonds",
                "Mark Reynolds",
                "Reggie Jackson",
                "Jay Buhner"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        }
    ]
}